(self.webpackChunk_N_E=self.webpackChunk_N_E||[]).push([[599],{5896:function(e,s,a){"use strict";a.r(s),a.d(s,{default:function(){return r}});var n=a(9008),t=a(7294),i=[{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how buidl the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"093909"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"009039"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"090089"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"01010101"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"092299"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"2222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09922099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222292099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0998999099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09459099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0912219099"}],o=a(5893),r=function(e){var s=(0,t.useState)(0),a=s[0],r=s[1],l=new Map;return(0,o.jsxs)("div",{children:[(0,o.jsxs)(n.default,{children:[(0,o.jsx)("title",{children:"Solana Scaffold"}),(0,o.jsx)("meta",{name:"description",content:"Quest Topix"})]}),(0,o.jsx)("div",{className:"flex justify-center h-full w-full",children:(0,o.jsx)("div",{className:"flex w-3/4 h-full justify-evenly bg-black bg-opacity-50 backdrop-blur-xl rounded drop-shadow-lg text-white m-5 rounded",children:(0,o.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex flex-col justify-center items-center",children:[(0,o.jsx)("div",{className:"text-xl font-bold",children:"Quest"}),(0,o.jsx)("div",{className:"text-lg text-white",children:i[a].question}),(0,o.jsx)("div",{className:"text-md flex flex-col mx-10",children:i[a].answers.map((function(e,s){return(0,o.jsxs)("button",{className:"answerBtn",onClick:function(){console.log(e),l.set(a,e),console.log(l.get(a))},children:[" ",e]},s)}))}),(0,o.jsxs)("div",{className:"text-md text-white",children:[(0,o.jsx)("button",{className:"backBtn",onClick:function(){return r(a-1)},children:"Prev"}),(0,o.jsx)("button",{className:"answerBtn",onClick:function(){return r(a+1)},children:"Next"})]})]})})})]})}},7106:function(e,s,a){(window.__NEXT_P=window.__NEXT_P||[]).push(["/quest",function(){return a(5896)}])}},function(e){e.O(0,[774,888,179],(function(){return s=7106,e(e.s=s);var s}));var s=e.O();_N_E=s}]);